<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes on rk</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Recipes on rk</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biscuits</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/tiramisu/</guid><description>Ingredients:
2c flour 1 tbsp baking powder 1/4 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp salt 6 tbsp butter 1c buttermilk Directions:
Combine dry ingredients Cut in butter, use pastry cutter until butter is about pea-sized Add buttermilk, stirring until barely combined Knead on floured counter 10-ish times Roll to 1/2&amp;quot; and cut biscuits Bake at 450F for 10-12 min</description></item><item><title>Butternut Squash Soup</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients:
1 butternut squash 1 large yellow onion vegetable stock (or water) tomato (fresh, paste, or canned; about 15oz canned or a few tbsp paste) 1 bay leaf (optional) 1 package cream cheese seasonings: salt, black pepper, herbs (rosemary, thyme, generic italian), garlic powder, onion powder, paprika (small amount), chili powder (small amount) alternate: omit cream cheese, use brown sugar, cinnamon, nutmeg, etc. as seasonings instead Directions:
Dice and saute onion in large soup pot Add cubed and peeled squash and cook for a few minutes Add stock or water until covered Add tomato, seasonings, and bay leaf Cover and simmer on low for 30-45 mins (the squash should be soft when done) Remove bay leaf Add cream cheese Blend with immersion blender until smooth Season to taste (I usually end up adding a bit more salt and chili powder at the end)</description></item><item><title>Cornbread</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/cornbread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/cornbread/</guid><description>Ingredients:
1c flour 1c cornmeal 2/3c sugar 1 tsp salt 3 1/2 tsp baking powder 1 egg 1c milk 1/3 c oil Bake 20-25min at 400F in greased 9&amp;quot; round</description></item><item><title>Enchiladas</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/enchiladas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/enchiladas/</guid><description>Ingredients:
1 medium yellow onion 1 bell pepper 1 can refried beans 1 can corn, whole kernel, drained sauce (any color, a 15oz can works) 8 tortillas cheese (cheddar/jack blend) (optional) chicken, steak, pork, or other meat for filling (optional) cilantro, lime, avocado, or diced tomato for garnish Variations:
green enchilada sauce, half of a shredded+sauted red cabbage for filling, omit bell pepper, omit corn Directions:
Thinly slice onion and pepper; season with cumin, chili powder, salt and saute on high heat to get char.</description></item><item><title>Pasta Carbonara</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/pasta-carbonara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/pasta-carbonara/</guid><description>Ingredients:
1 lb uncooked fettuccine 1/2 lb bacon 1 small yellow onion 4 cloves garlic 3 eggs 3/4 c parmesan 1/4 c cream Directions:
Chop and cook bacon. Remove bacon from pan, keep oil in pan. Saute diced onion in bacon oil. For last 30s-1min, add minced garlic. Remove from heat. Combine eggs, cream, parmesan, salt, and lots of black pepper. Cook pasta and drain. Immediately after draining pasta, put back in pot.</description></item><item><title>Savoiardi</title><link>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/savoiardi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arussellk.github.io/recipes/savoiardi/</guid><description>Ingredients:
70g egg white (about 2 large eggs) 45g yolk (just over 2 yolks) 62g sugar (granulated) 62g flour dash salt lemon zest Room temp eggs work best.
Directions:
Beat egg whites with sugar and salt until very stiff peaks Fold in egg yolks Fold in flour Pipe onto parchment Bake at 390F for 5-7 min</description></item></channel></rss>